<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Ashish Bende</title>
    <link>https://ashishbende.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Ashish Bende</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 22:42:29 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ashishbende.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rackspace</title>
      <link>https://ashishbende.com/blog/rackspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 22:42:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashishbende.com/blog/rackspace/</guid>
      <description>Rackspace Summer Internship I was an intern at Rackspace during the summer&#39;16. I worked with the ObjectRocket team, a relatively small but dedicated team. I was tasked to develop an end-to-end data connector project for managed database service (MongoDB/Elasticsearch). A bit intermediating at the beginning, but I thoroughly enjoyed working on this feature.
In a short span, I developed the connector which would consume real-time Twitter feeds and store them in either MongoDB or Elasticsearch instance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fujitsu</title>
      <link>https://ashishbende.com/blog/fujitsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 22:42:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashishbende.com/blog/fujitsu/</guid>
      <description>Fujitsu Network Communications At Fujitsu, I&amp;rsquo;m contributing to Virtuora-NC - an OpenDaylight based SDN controller. Over the years, I worked on different projects. Starting with the NorthBound, followed by MLPCE (where I spent most of my time) and, most recently, the Topology project.
Virtuora NC  Topology:  A module that discovers physical network inventory and builds topology representation. Developing a physical topology visualization feature across different abstraction layers to pinpoint exact network alarm events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ashishbende.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashishbende.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: contact@ashishbende.com LinkedIn: /in/ashishbende Github: @ashishbende  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ashishbende.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashishbende.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Fujitsu Virtuora-NC
 Rackspace Internship Twitter-to-Elasticsearch Dataconnector
 Personal Projects Simulations  Traffic simulation Battle Tank  Robotics  Robo Kinematics Home Service Robot Map my world Robot localization Rover  2D video games  tic-tac-toe flappy bird clone snakes ping-pong  RESTful Web Services / Distributed Systems  Overlay Network  Facebook Timemachine Voting Web App  HPC/CPU Parallelization  Climatological Windrose Generation  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
